fotoblow.com 2011-08-06

# privacy policy - FotoBlow

When you visit Fotoblow.com, we may collect passive information about your visit. Passive information is any form of aggregate data, navigational data, tracking data, click-stream data, or historical data. It may include referral data (e.g., the address of the last URL you visited prior to clicking through to the Site) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Firefox browser on a Macintosh platform). We use this information to track how users are accessing and using the website.

In addition, when you visit the Site we generally collect the IP Address of the computer you are using to access the Site. (An IP, or 'Internet Protocol,' address is a unique number associated with your computer, that may be communicated to other computers and servers when you use the Internet.) We use this information for purposes of security and anti-fraud protection.

Fotoblow also uses cookies and/or web beacons. (A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, and that may be accessed when you use a website. A web beacon is a small, transparent graphic image placed on a website, which allows the site to record the actions of a visitor opening the page that contains the beacon.)

We may use cookies or web beacons to: (1) determine whether visitors to the Site are unique, or whether the same user is visiting the site on multiple occassions; (2) help deliver advertisements; (3) track usage throughout the Site (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Site, etc.); (4) store your agreement to the terms and conditions for entering and using the Site; (5) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.

These kinds of information do not, on their own, personally identify you. However, they can potentially be combined with information obtained from other sources in order to identify you. Fotoblow does not ordinarily seek or obtain personally identifying information about users from others. It does reserve the right to seek such information in the event of a violation of the Fotoblow Terms and Conditions, in the event of a dispute between Fotoblow and you, or if required by law to do so.

### Content You Submit to or Post on the website

Fotoblow allows you to submit and post audio and video content, and accompanying text ('User Content'). User Content that you submit to Fotoblow or post on the Site, including any personal information included in your User Content, becomes publicly available and can be seen, collected, and used by others. You should not post any content on the Site that you do not want to be seen, collected, or used by others.

In the process of posting User Content, you may be asked to provide some personally identifying information, such as your name and e-mail address, and other documentation. We will keep a record of the information you provide, including your personally identifiable information, and that information will be linked in our records to the User Content. We will not publically post your name or other personally identifying information, and we will not provide such information to our advertisers or business partners without your permission.

### Use of Visitor Information Collected on the website

We do not collect or share personally identifiable information about visitors to the site through the ordinary operation of the website. We may obtain and merge information about users and usage of the Site into aggregated data, which may then be used by us and/or shared with advertisers or others. When we provide aggregated information to outside companies, they will not be able to identify you or contact you based on that data.

### Usage Information - Collection and Use by Advertisers and Others

Fotoblow allows other companies to place advertisements on the Site. These companies use technology to deliver advertisements you see on the Site directly to your browser. In doing so, they may automatically receive your IP address. Other companies that place advertising on the Site may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information, including information about your usage of the Site. We do not control the processes that advertisers use to collect information. However, IP addresses, cookies and web beacons alone generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or content may appear on the Site generally will not know who you are unless you provide additional information to them, by responding to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by some other means.

### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about Fotoblow's Privacy Policy and use of personal information, please contact us here.
